[
  {
    "Question": "Can EnglishClub help us find students?",
    "Answer": "Yes. You can add a free listing in our [English schools directory](https://www.englishclub.com/esl-world/). You can also [advertise with EnglishClub](https://www.englishclub.com/advertise/).",
    "Source": "https://www.englishclub.com/about/faq-schools.php\r",
    "Category": "Category-1"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Can EnglishClub help us find teachers?",
    "Answer": "We have a [TEFL Jobs](https://www.tefl.net/jobs/international/) section for this on our sister site TEFL.net.",
    "Source": "https://www.englishclub.com/about/faq-schools.php\r",
    "Category": "Category-2"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Can we link our Self Access Centre to EnglishClub?",
    "Answer": "Yes. Many schools and universities build links to EnglishClub into their courses and learning resources. You can link from your own intranet or web site direct to any pages you wish. For example, you could link to [English Grammar](https://www.englishclub.com/grammar/) as a general link, or to [Tense](https://www.englishclub.com/grammar/tense.htm) as a more specific link, or to [Present Perfect Tense](https://www.englishclub.com/grammar/verb-tenses_present-perfect.htm) as a very specific link.",
    "Source": "https://www.englishclub.com/about/faq-schools.php\r",
    "Category": "Category-3"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Hi",
    "Answer": "Hello",
    "Source": "Editorial\r",
    "Category": "Category-4"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Do I need a ticket to travel?",
    "Answer": "Yes, youll need a valid ticket (or permit to travel) to travel on our trains. If you travel on a train without a ticket, youll be asked to pay the full single or return fare or, may be given a penalty fare.",
    "Source": "https://www.southernrailway.com/help-and-support/contact-us/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-4"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What can I do if my season ticket is lost, stolen or damaged?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\n### Lost or stolen tickets \\n\\n Please report a lost or stolen season ticket to a Southern Railway ticket office as soon as possible. You should also report any theft to the police. \\n\\nIf your ticket is valid for a month or more well issue a replacement the first time you lose it within a 12 month period. \\n\\nWe may also issue a second replacement if the first was stolen or destroyed in a fire, or there are other exceptional circumstances. In this case, you must apply in writing and supply police or fire service evidence. \\n\\n We wont issue more than two duplicates in 12 months. \\n\\nYoull have to pay an administration fee of Â£20 for a duplicate ticket.\\n\\nWe wont issue duplicates for weekly season tickets.\\n\\n###  Damaged tickets\\n\\n If your ticket is faded or damaged, or doesnt work in automatic ticket barriers, you can return it to any Gatwick Express, Great Northern, Southern or Thameslink ticket office where well happily replace it free of charge.\\n",
    "Source": "https://www.southernrailway.com/help-and-support/contact-us/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-4"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Do your stations have car parks?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nMany of our stations have car parks managed by Indigo. You can get more information and buy weekly, monthly or annual season tickets online in our [car parking section](https://www.southernrailway.com/travel-information/plan-your-journey/car-parking). \\n\\n### Contact Indigo\\n\\nWebsite: [www.southernrailwayparking.com](http://www.southernrailwayparking.com/)\\n\\nCall: 0330 1235 247\\n\\n Email: [customersupport.uk@parkindigo.com](mailto:customersupport.uk@parkindigo.com)\\n\\nWrite to: Customer Support Centre PO Box 2466 Watford WD18 1XH\\n",
    "Source": "https://www.southernrailway.com/help-and-support/contact-us/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-4"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Are your trains accessible for people with disabilities?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nAll of our trains can be used by people with disabilities. We offer an assisted travel service if you need help at our stations to get the train - for example a wheelchair ramp.\\n\\nPlease call us to check that the stations and services youre using are obstruction free 24-hours before you travel or to organise assistance. \\n\\n Find out more about [assisted travel](https://www.southernrailway.com/travel-information/travel-help/assisted-travel)\\n\\n Get a copy of our [Disabled Persons Protection Policy](https://www.southernrailway.com/-/media/goahead/gtr-all-shared-pdfs-and-documents/making-rail-accessible---helping-older-and-disabled-passengers.pdf?la=en)\\n",
    "Source": "https://www.southernrailway.com/help-and-support/contact-us/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-4"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Can I take my bike on your trains?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nIf you have a folding bike, you can take it folded onto any train and at any time. \\n\\nWe cant always accommodate non-folding bikes. You can bring non-folding cycles on many of our trains. But during the busy morning and afternoon commuting hours, space on board is at a premium. \\n\\nYou cant take a bike on rail replacement bus services. \\n\\n Get more information in our [bike policy](https://www.southernrailway.com/travel-information/on-board/bringing-a-bike)\\n",
    "Source": "https://www.southernrailway.com/help-and-support/contact-us/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-4"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why is my train overcrowded?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nWe run as many peak-time trains as we can on the railway infrastructure. We adjust our timetables and the number of carriages where we can to reduce overcrowding, and were continuing to develop and improve both our train fleet and our network to improve things further. \\n\\n Trains can be busier than usual for a number of reasons. An earlier cancellation, for instance, will mean the next service will have more passengers than usual. Sometimes, trains have fewer coaches than usual because weve had to temporarily withdraw some carriages for emergency repairs. \\n\\nSee which peak-time trains are most likely to have seats available on our routes in our guide to [finding a quieter train](https://www.southernrailway.com/travel-information/travel-help/finding-a-quieter-train). \\n",
    "Source": "https://www.southernrailway.com/help-and-support/contact-us/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-4"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is Twitter?",
    "Answer": "Twitter is a service for friends, family, and coworkers to communicate and stay connected through the exchange of quick, frequent messages. People post Tweets, which may contain photos, videos, links, and text. These messages are posted to your profile, sent to your [followers](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/following-faqs), and are searchable on Twitter search. Learn more about [how to use Twitter](https://help.twitter.com/en/twitter-guide).",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-4"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Do I need anything special to use it?",
    "Answer": "All you need to use Twitter is an internet connection or a mobile phone. Join us here! Once youre in, begin finding and following accounts whose Tweets interest you. Well recommend great accounts once youre signed up.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-5"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Whats a Tweet?",
    "Answer": "A Tweet is any message posted to Twitter which may contain photos, videos, links, and text. Click or tap the Tweet button to post the update to your profile. Read our [Posting a Tweet](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/how-to-tweet) article for more information.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-5"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How can I send updates to Twitter?",
    "Answer": "Read our article about [how to post a Tweet](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/how-to-tweet). You can Tweet from twitter.com, a mobile device, or an application.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-5"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Whats a Retweet?",
    "Answer": "A [Retweet](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/retweet-faqs) is a Tweet that you forward to your followers.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-5"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do I post a picture to Twitter?",
    "Answer": "Uploading and sharing images on Twitter is easy! Find step-by-step instructions and FAQs on [how to post a picture on Twitter](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/tweeting-gifs-and-pictures).",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-5"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Can I edit a Tweet once Ive posted it?",
    "Answer": "No, you cant edit a Tweet once you have posted it, but you can [delete your Tweet](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/delete-tweets).",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-5"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How can I enable night mode?",
    "Answer": "To enable night mode via twitter.com, click on your profile photo, then select Night mode from the drop-down menu. To disable night mode, simply click on the Night mode setting again. Night mode is also available on [Twitter for iOS](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/twitter-ios-app#night-mode) and [Twitter for Android.](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/twitter-for-android-faqs#night)",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-5"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who reads my updates?",
    "Answer": "Your followers read your Tweets. If your Tweets are public, anyone who runs a search for a keyword in your Tweet may be able to see that message. Your Tweets are public by default; if youre hesitant to have people you may not know read your updates, [protect your Tweets](https://help.twitter.com/en/safety-and-security/public-and-protected-tweets) to approve followers and keep your updates out of search.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-5"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why cant I see all my Tweets? Are they lost?",
    "Answer": "We store all your Tweets. Navigate to your profile to view up to 3,200 of your most recent Tweets in your profile timeline. To view more, you can [download your Twitter Archive](https://help.twitter.com/en/managing-your-account/how-to-download-your-twitter-archive) and browse a snapshot of your Twitter information, starting with your first Tweet.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-5"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Can I put my Twitter updates on my blog?",
    "Answer": "Yes! Put a [Twitter widget](https://twitter.com/settings/widgets) on your blog or website - anywhere that accepts Javascript or HTML.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-5"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What does it mean to follow someone on Twitter?",
    "Answer": "[Following](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/following-faqs) someone means youve chosen to subscribe to their Twitter updates. When you follow someone, every time they post a new message, it will appear on your Twitter Home timeline.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-5"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do I find people to follow?",
    "Answer": "When you create an account, you can [search for people](https://twitter.com/#!/who_to_follow/suggestions) by name or username, [import friends](https://twitter.com/#!/who_to_follow/import) from other networks, or [invite friends via email](https://twitter.com/#!/who_to_follow/import).",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-6"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do I know who Im following?",
    "Answer": "After you click or tap the Follow button on someones profile, youre following them. See a list of people youre following by clicking on the [following](https://twitter.com/#!/following) link on your profile page or on your home pages sidebar.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-6"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do I know who is following me?",
    "Answer": "Twitter sends you a notification when someone new follows you. Set up your [email preferences](https://help.twitter.com/en/managing-your-account/updating-email-preferences) and [mobile push notifications](https://help.twitter.com/en/managing-your-account/notifications-on-mobile-devices) to notify you when you have a new follower. The [Followers](https://twitter.com/followers) link on your profile page will also tell you who is following you.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-6"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What are follow limits?",
    "Answer": "Twitter has follow and update limits for stability and abuse control. Learn more about [follow limits](https://help.twitter.com/en/rules-and-policies/twitter-limits).",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-6"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What are replies?",
    "Answer": "A [reply](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/mentions-and-replies) is a response to another persons Tweet. Click or tap the reply icon on another persons Tweet to reply to it. Please note that if your Tweets are protected, people who are not following you will not see your replies or mentions.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-7"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the difference between a reply and a Direct Message?",
    "Answer": "A [reply](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/mentions-and-replies) is a public message sent regardless of follow-ship. Anyone can view it (if your Tweets are public). A [Direct Message](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/direct-messages) is a private message, and can only be seen by the sender and intended recipients.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-7"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What are Direct Messages?",
    "Answer": "[Direct Messages](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/direct-messages) are private messages sent from one Twitter account to other Twitter account(s), and they do not appear in public for anyone else to read. You can start a conversation with anyone who follows you.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-7"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why are accounts suspended?",
    "Answer": "Accounts are suspended for [Terms of Service](https://twitter.com/tos?lang=en) violations or spam investigation. Read more [about account suspension](https://help.twitter.com/en/managing-your-account/suspended-twitter-accounts).",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-7"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do I report spam?",
    "Answer": "Read our article about [how to report spam on Twitter](https://help.twitter.com/en/safety-and-security/report-spam). We encourage you to always block any spammers you find.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-7"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Where can I find out more information about Twitters Terms of Service?",
    "Answer": "Read Twitters [Terms of Service](https://twitter.com/tos?lang=en) and the [Twitter Rules](https://help.twitter.com/en/rules-and-policies/twitter-rules) for more information.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do I submit a complaint about copyright, impersonation, trademark, or other Terms of Service issues?",
    "Answer": "Review our [Terms of Service section](https://help.twitter.com/en/rules-and-policies/twitter-trademark-policy) to find out what constitutes a violation, and how to go about fixing a related problem.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Hi",
    "Answer": "Hello",
    "Source": "Editorial\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is GitHub Enterprise?",
    "Answer": "GitHub Enterprise is the on-premises version of [GitHub.com](https://github.com/home). It makes collaborative coding possible and enjoyable for large-scale enterprise software development teams. A full list of specs and features are detailed on our [data sheet](https://enterprise.github.com/downloads/en/enterprise-datasheet.pdf).",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How is GitHub Enterprise different from",
    "Answer": "[GitHub.com](http://github.com/)?",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Can I evaluate GitHub Enterprise within my organization before purchasing?",
    "Answer": "Yes. 45-day evaluation licenses are available and may be upgraded to full licenses at any time during the trial period. To get started, [try GitHub for free](https://enterprise.github.com/trial). Well contact you shortly after with information on downloading the software and installing trial license keys.",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What hardware and software are required?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nGitHub Enterprise is delivered as a virtual appliance that includes all software required to get up and running. The only additional software required is a compatible virtual machine environment.\\n\\nThe following minimal hardware requirements are suggested for production deployments:\\n\\n*   Processor: Two 3.0 GHz CPU cores (or virtual equivalent) \\n*   Memory: 14-16 GB (minimum dependent on selected platform) \\n*   Disk: \\n\\n    *   200 GB VM root partition \\n    *   100 GB data partition (our recommendation, actual size depends on your data) \\n*   Storage: High-performance SAN or locally attached storage",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is a Virtual Appliance?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nYou can think of a virtual appliance as the equivalent of a network appliance that you might buy, mount in a rack, and plug into your network. The only difference is that it runs as a virtual machine inside of VMware or some other virtualization platform rather than as a physical device you mount in a rack.\\n\\nThis saves time (you can download the appliance and all updates immediately) and space (you just add it to your existing virtualization infrastructure). It also makes managing, backing up, and restoring the appliance easy because you can use your virtualization platforms built-in snapshotting capabilities. \\n\\nYou can learn more about virtual appliances [here](http://www.vmware.com/appliances/getting-started/learn/overview.html).\\n",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which Virtual Machine environments are supported?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nWe currently support the following environments.\\nPlatformImage Format[VMware](https://www.vmware.com/)[OVF](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Open_Virtualization_Format)[OpenStack KVM](https://www.openstack.org/)[QCOW2](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Qcow#qcow2)[XenServer](http://www.xenserver.org/)[VHD](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/VHD_(file_format)#Software_support)[Hyper-V](https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/server-cloud/solutions/virtualization.aspx)[VHD](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/VHD_(file_format)#Software_support)[Microsoft Azure](https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/)[VHD](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/VHD_(file_format)#Software_support)[Amazon Web Services (AWS)](https://aws.amazon.com/)[AMI](https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/AMIs.html)[Google Cloud Platform (GCP)](https://cloud.google.com/)[Google Compute Engine (GCE) image](https://cloud.google.com/compute/docs/images)\\n\\nPlease [contact us](https://enterprise.github.com/contact) if we dont support your environment.\\n",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Does GitHub Enterprise support clustering?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nYes, as of [GitHub Enterprise 2.5](https://enterprise.github.com/releases/2.5.0). However, clustering is designed for specific scaling situations and is not intended for every organization.\\n\\nPlease refer to the [Clustering Guide](https://help.github.com/enterprise/admin/guides/clustering) to learn more about clustering.\\n",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Is clustering right for my organization?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nClustering provides better scalability by distributing load across multiple nodes. This horizontal scaling may be preferable for some organizations with tens of thousands of developers. However, setting up a redundant and scalable cluster can be complex and requires careful planning. This additional complexity will need to be planned for during installation, disaster recovery scenarios, and upgrades.\\n\\nGitHub Enterprise requires low latency between nodes and is not intended for redundancy across geographic locations.\\n\\nClustering provides redundancy, but it is not intended to replace the [High Availability Configuration](https://help.github.com/enterprise/admin/guides/installation/high-availability-configuration). A primary/secondary failover configuration is far simpler than clustering and will serve the needs of many organizations.\\n",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do I get access to clustering?",
    "Answer": "Clustering is designed for specific scaling situations and is not intended for every organization. If clustering is something youd like to consider, please contact your dedicated representative or our [account management team](mailto:sales@github.com) at [sales@github.com](mailto:sales@github.com).",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Can we authenticate users with our LDAP directory or identity access management system?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\n Yes. GitHub Enterprise supports external user authentication via LDAP, CAS, or SAML. The setup process includes a step for configuring your organizations identity management information. \\n\\nBy default, GitHub Enterprise runs in a self-contained authentication mode with user information stored in the GitHub Enterprise database. LDAP, SAML, or CAS is not required.\\n",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which LDAP providers are supported?",
    "Answer": "GitHub Enterprise supports any provider that follows the LDAP specification. See [this article](https://help.github.com/enterprise/admin/guides/user-management/using-ldap/#supported-ldap-services) for a full list of supported providers.",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which SAML providers are supported?",
    "Answer": "GitHub Enterprise supports any provider that follows the SAML 2.0 standard. See [this article](https://help.github.com/enterprise/admin/guides/user-management/using-saml/) for a full list of supported providers.",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do I control access to Git repositories?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nThe product includes a number of features that provide granular control over repository access. Each repository may specify the following general access rights for each team or collaborator:\\n\\n*   Admin: Full access to the repository, including the ability to control access for other users.\\n*   Read + Write: Users may push changes into the repository and pull changes from the repository.\\n*   Read-only: Users may browse the repository via the web interface and use Git to fetch changes but may not push into the repository.\\n\\nIn addition to these access levels, you can use protected branches inside a repository to prevent force pushes to specific branches. You can also define individuals or teams who are allowed to push to a branch, preventing others from making changes.\\n\\nRequired statuses offer more control over changes made in protected branches. Using required statuses, you can disable the ability to merge changes into protected branches until certain CI checks pass.\\n\\nGitHub Enterprise ships with the same [collaboration features for Organizations](https://github.com/features) found on GitHub.com. These simplify the process of managing access for teams of users that you define.\\n",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Hi",
    "Answer": "Hello",
    "Source": "Editorial\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "May I copy and use any material that I find on EnglishClub?",
    "Answer": "You may print and distribute any material that you find on EnglishClub for non-commercial educational purposes provided that you do not modify its content and provided that you mention EnglishClub.com as the source.",
    "Source": "https://www.englishclub.com/about/faq-teachers.php\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Can EnglishClub help me find a job?",
    "Answer": "We have a [TEFL Jobs](https://www.tefl.net/jobs/international/) section for this on our sister site TEFL.net.",
    "Source": "https://www.englishclub.com/about/faq-teachers.php\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "I need some ideas for lesson plans urgently.",
    "Answer": "You can find many ideas for lessons, including games, activities and worksheets, graded by level, in our [Teach English](https://www.englishclub.com/teach/) pages. But dont forget that there are also hundreds of resources that you can use or adapt in our [Learn English](https://www.englishclub.com/learn-english.htm) section.",
    "Source": "https://www.englishclub.com/about/faq-teachers.php\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Id like to set up a chat session with a teacher and students from another school.",
    "Answer": "Good idea! You can run chat sessions from the [ESL Chat](https://www.englishclub.com/esl-chat/) page. But first, you probably want to contact other teachers, maybe in another country, who want to do the same. You will need to synchronize your chat session so that both schools log on at the same time. You can find other teachers in our [School Projects](https://www.englishclub.com/tefl-forums/viewforum.php?f=1) forum.",
    "Source": "https://www.englishclub.com/about/faq-teachers.php\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Id like to find pen pals for my students.",
    "Answer": "Another excellent idea. You can find other teachers looking for exchange pen pals in our [School Projects](https://www.englishclub.com/tefl-forums/viewforum.php?f=1) forum.",
    "Source": "https://www.englishclub.com/about/faq-teachers.php\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Id like to discuss some teaching issues with other teachers.",
    "Answer": "Check out the [Teacher Forums](https://www.englishclub.com/tefl-forums/), where you can read and write posts on a variety of teaching topics.",
    "Source": "https://www.englishclub.com/about/faq-teachers.php\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do I submit a lesson plan?",
    "Answer": "If you have a good lesson plan that youd like to share with other teachers, [please submit it here](https://www.englishclub.com/efl/guest/).",
    "Source": "https://www.englishclub.com/about/faq-teachers.php\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "I want to learn more about TEFL qualifications.",
    "Answer": "Youll find details about various TEFL courses and qualifications under [TEFL Training](https://www.englishclub.com/tefl-training/).",
    "Source": "https://www.englishclub.com/about/faq-teachers.php\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Hi",
    "Answer": "Hello",
    "Source": "Editorial\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How can I use EnglishClub to improve my English?",
    "Answer": "EnglishClub has many pages designed to help you improve your English. EnglishClub is like a Self Access Centre - it lets you work in your own way and at your own time. You can choose the method that you like best. If you like to study, you can look at the lessons in areas like [Grammar](https://www.englishclub.com/grammar/), [Vocabulary](https://www.englishclub.com/vocabulary/) and [Pronunciation](https://www.englishclub.com/pronunciation/), or the four skills, [Listening](https://www.englishclub.com/listening/), [Speaking](https://www.englishclub.com/speaking/), [Reading](https://www.englishclub.com/reading/), [Writing](https://www.englishclub.com/writing/). If you prefer a fun method, you can try areas such as [ESL Games](https://www.englishclub.com/esl-games/), [ESL Quizzes](https://www.englishclub.com/esl-quizzes/) and [ESL Jokes](https://www.englishclub.com/esl-jokes/). For a really interactive approach, try communicating in English through [ESL Forums](https://www.englishclub.com/esl-forums/) or [MyEnglishClub](https://www.myenglishclub.com/). You can also post a question about English at the [Grammar Help Desk](https://www.englishclub.com/esl-forums/viewforum.php?f=199).",
    "Source": "https://www.englishclub.com/about/faq-learners.php\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Does EnglishClub offer language courses?",
    "Answer": "EnglishClub is an ESL resource site, with many pages and lessons that can help you improve your English. But these are not language courses as such. If you are looking for a language course at a school, or perhaps online, you could check our [English schools directory](https://www.englishclub.com/esl-world/)",
    "Source": "https://www.englishclub.com/about/faq-learners.php\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "I have a question about grammar. Can you help me?",
    "Answer": "You can ask a grammar question on our [Grammar Help Desk](https://www.englishclub.com/esl-forums/viewforum.php?f=199)",
    "Source": "https://www.englishclub.com/about/faq-learners.php\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How can I listen to English with EnglishClub?",
    "Answer": "You can find several listening resources in [English Listening](https://www.englishclub.com/listening/)",
    "Source": "https://www.englishclub.com/about/faq-learners.php\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How can I chat in English?",
    "Answer": "You can chat in English night or day through [ESL Chat](https://www.englishclub.com/esl-chat/)",
    "Source": "https://www.englishclub.com/about/faq-learners.php\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "I want to find a pen pal to exchange emails in English.",
    "Answer": "Youll find plenty of other learners and teachers who want to hear from you in [MyEnglishClub](https://www.myenglishclub.com/)",
    "Source": "https://www.englishclub.com/about/faq-learners.php\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Where can I discuss things in English?",
    "Answer": "You can discuss anything you want in English in EnglishClubs [ESL Forums](https://www.englishclub.com/esl-forums/) or in [MyEnglishClub](https://www.myenglishclub.com/).",
    "Source": "https://www.englishclub.com/about/faq-learners.php\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "I dont know my level in English. Can you tell me?",
    "Answer": "You can get a good idea of your level in English by doing the [written comprehension test](https://www.englishclub.com/reading/test.htm)",
    "Source": "https://www.englishclub.com/about/faq-learners.php\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "I need help with pronunciation.",
    "Answer": "You can find some useful pages in our [Pronunciation section](https://www.englishclub.com/pronunciation/), which includes word stress, sentence stress and linking.",
    "Source": "https://www.englishclub.com/about/faq-learners.php\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Id like to play some games to improve my English.",
    "Answer": "Games are an excellent way to make progress in English. Play games in [ESL Games](https://www.englishclub.com/esl-games/)",
    "Source": "https://www.englishclub.com/about/faq-learners.php\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Can I do some ESL quizzes for fun?",
    "Answer": "Certainly! Check out [ESL Quizzes](https://www.englishclub.com/esl-quizzes/) for plenty of interactive quizzes.",
    "Source": "https://www.englishclub.com/about/faq-learners.php\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Can EnglishClub help me find a school?",
    "Answer": "If youre looking for a school almost anywhere in the world, try looking in our [English schools directory](https://www.englishclub.com/esl-world/)",
    "Source": "https://www.englishclub.com/about/faq-learners.php\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Hi",
    "Answer": "Hello",
    "Source": "Editorial\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "My app has already been reviewed, do I still need to go through app review?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nOn May 1, 2018 we announced a new [App Review process](https://developers.facebook.com/blog/post/2018/05/01/enhanced-developer-app-review-and-graph-api-3.0-now-live/)that is required for FB Login (extended permissions) and the 6 APIs (Pages, Messenger, Business Manager, Instagram, Groups and Events). App Review submission for these APIs/permissions is required before August 1, 2018 in order to maintain access to those APIs. On August 1st, we will begin enforcing this deadline for inactive apps.\\n\\nFor active apps that require these permissions, we will auto-enroll apps into the app review process in the coming weeks. You can [read more about this announcement here](https://developers.facebook.com/blog/post/2018/07/31/facebook-app-review-update/).\\n\\nOn July 2, 2018, we announced additional APIs that require app review: Marketing API and Lead Ads Retrieval. App Review submission for these APIs/permissions is required before February 1, 2019 in order to maintain access. You can [read more about the due dates here](https://developers.facebook.com/blog/post/2018/07/02/app-review-deadlines-approaching/).\\n",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is happening on August 1st?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nAs we announced [earlier this year](https://developers.facebook.com/blog/post/2018/05/01/enhanced-developer-app-review-and-graph-api-3.0-now-live/), all apps accessing the Pages API, Groups API, Events API, Business Manager API, Instagram Graph API, Messenger Platform, and Facebook Login were expected to submit for [app review](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review) by August 1.\\n\\nTo help protect the integrity of our platform, we have removed API access for apps that require these permissions, have not gone through app review, and have not been active within the last 28 days as of July 31, 2018. If you still need access to our APIs, we encourage you to submit for review through your apps [App Dashboard](https://developers.facebook.com/apps).\\n\\nAll active apps that require these permissions will be auto-enrolled in app review in the coming weeks. Developers will be notified if we require additional information to complete the app review submission. If responses are not received in the allocated timeframe, reviewable API access will be disabled.\\n",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "I am an independent developer and my apps use reviewable permissions with an August 1st deadline. Will my apps be auto-enrolled in App Review?",
    "Answer": "Yes, if your apps have made calls to the Graph API in the last 28 days as of July 31, 2018 and require access to the reviewable permissions with an August 1st deadline, your app will be auto-enrolled in the app review process. We will notify you when we have a process available to send us the additional information needed to complete the review process.",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "I have an app that only leverages assets I own. App Review is not something Ive had to do before. Am I required to submit for review? Will my app be automatically enrolled in App Review post August 1st?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nYes, ALL apps that leverage permissions that require review (Pages API, Groups API, Events API, Business Manager API, Instagram Graph API, Messenger Platform, extended Facebook Login permissions, Marketing API and Lead Ads API) must submit for app review in adherence with the communicated deadlines.\\n\\nActive apps that leverage permissions with an August 1st deadline (Pages API, Groups API, Events API, Business Manager API, Instagram Graph API, Messenger Platform, extended Facebook Login permissions) and have not yet proactively submitted for review will be auto-enrolled in the review process. You can accelerate the App Review process by submitting your app for review prior to auto-enrollment. This will give you more control over when your app is reviewed and what information is used for the review.\\n",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What if I have several apps, will they all need to be reviewed?",
    "Answer": "The need for app review is based on the App ID level. Each individual app using those permissions or features must be submitted for review.",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What does the app review process entail?",
    "Answer": "For more details, visit [this page](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review). The process will give you the opportunity to provide details on which permissions you need, and how they will be used. Facebook will review the use case and determine if it is permissible under our policy. After permission review, depending on the API/permission we may have additional requirements such as business verification and contract signing.",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Will test apps inherit reviewable permissions from parent apps?",
    "Answer": "Yes, [test apps](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/test-apps) will inherit reviewable permissions from parent apps.",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "As Facebook announces additional APIs that need to go through App Review, do I need to re-submit for the entire App Review and Business Verification process all over again?",
    "Answer": "As new APIs become available, these will need to be requested through App Review. Business Verification however, is only required once per Business Manager entity, so Business Verification will not be required again if new permissions or APIs are required for an app.",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If there are multiple Business Manager accounts for my business, do I need to verify all Business Managers?",
    "Answer": "As of August 1, 2018, you only need to verify the Business Manager which the app is connected to.",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How will you verify my business?",
    "Answer": "As part of the review process, you may be asked for business information such as the legal name of the business, address and phone number. In addition, you may be requested to provide business documentation such as utility bills, licenses, certificates of formation, or articles of incorporation.",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How long will it take to review my app?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nAt the moment we are dealing with increased volume. The entire process may take up to several weeks.\\n\\n*   Permission review may take up to several weeks. Our latest update on timelines can be found [here](https://developers.facebook.com/blog/post/2018/07/02/app-review-deadlines-approaching/).\\n*   Business verification should take a few days, however it will depend on the quality of documentation.\\n*   Contract signing can be completed as soon as you have your designated officer sign the contract.",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do I know my status throughout the process?",
    "Answer": "You can always find the status of business verification and contracts and steps to take in the business verification panel found in the app review tab of the app dashboard. We will send you notifications throughout the process to let you know what action is needed.",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who should sign the Supplemental Terms For Extended Platform Products and Tech Provider Amendment contracts?",
    "Answer": "The person signing the contracts must have the legal authority to bind your business. For example, an officer or other authorized signatory of your business.",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If an agency or developer manages my app and ads, who needs to go through business verification?",
    "Answer": "The app should be linked to the Business Manager for the business that ultimately owns the app and has access to the data being generated from the app. This business should be the one who goes through the business verification process.",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If I have multiple apps at different tiers (for test purposes), do they all need to go through app review and business verification?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nApp review must be performed per app. We recommend that you review your app dashboard to get the specific list of permissions that require review.\\n\\nBusiness Verification is required once per Business Manager. If you choose to associate all your apps with the same Business Manager, then you will only need to go through business verification once.\\n",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "I have multiple Business Manager accounts, which one should I use?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nIf you already have a Business Manager account, we recommend that you connect the app to the existing Business Manager.\\n\\nIf there are multiple Business Manager accounts that belong to the business, we recommend determining the rationale for multiple Business Manager accounts and aligning the app with the most appropriate Business Manager. If the business has a credit line set up through the Business Manager, we recommend that you connect the app with the one that has the credit line.\\n",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Do mobile app advertisers need to go through app review in order to set up an SDK?",
    "Answer": "The App Review process refers to apps that require certain API permissions. You can [read about the permissions required for review here](https://developers.facebook.com/blog/post/2018/07/02/app-review-deadlines-approaching/). Setting up the SDK itself does not require app review. However, the SDK does enable apps to make calls to Facebook APIs, and if those APIs require review, the app will need to submit for app review.",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What should I include in the app review submission for Lead Retrieval and/or Marketing API? Im supposed to upload a screencast but my app doesnt involve a UI (e.g. Lead Retrieval API connects on the backend).",
    "Answer": "You can provide a screencast of your integration, or if your app does not have an end user experience, you can provide a minimum of 2 screenshots which show the settings view of your page, your CRM or Business Manager as well as provide a Page ID for a page youll be using through these products. You can read more about this option [here](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/server-to-server-apps).",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What permissions will I need to request?",
    "Answer": "You will need to request the `leads_retrieval` and `manage_pages` permissions.",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who needs to go through the review process?",
    "Answer": "If the clients are also the owner of the app, then they, themselves go through the process as direct developers. If the clients have a third party developer as the owner of the app, then its the developer who will go through the review.",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "My app used to access public content on pages, am I affected by the v3.0 changes?",
    "Answer": "Yes. Apps that access content of public pages need to request Page Public Content Access feature and require review by Facebook.",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Is my Messenger bot affected by the v3.0 changes?",
    "Answer": "Yes. In v3.0, all Messenger Platform APIs are included under Pages_messaging permission and require review.",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "My app uses the publish_actions permission to post stories. Is it affected by v3.0?",
    "Answer": "The `publish_actions` permission is deprecated in Graph API v3.0. Apps can still post stories via mediated experiences like the Facebook Share Dialog on the web, or the Share Sheets for iOS and Android. Apps can publish to groups through the `publish_groups` permission, which requires an app go through review.",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "My app uses the user_managed_groups permission. Is it affected by v3.0?",
    "Answer": "The `user_managed_groups` permission is deprecated in Graph API v3.0. Apps can use the new Groups API, along with the `publish_groups` and `read_groups_user_data` permissions in its place. The new API and permissions require apps go through review by Facebook.",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "My app used to access events. Is it affected by v3.0?",
    "Answer": "In Graph API v3.0, apps that access events need to use the `user_events` permission. Apps that use that permission will need to be reviewed by Facebook.",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "My app uses the Instagram API. Is it affected by v3.0?",
    "Answer": "The Instagram API is not affected by Graph API v3.0. However, all apps that use the Instagram API need to be reviewed by Facebook.",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "My app used Facebook Login. Is it affected by the v3.0 launch?",
    "Answer": "Yes. Apps can access only a users name, email address, and profile picture without App Review. All other permissions will require review by Facebook.",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "My app uses Facebooks Marketing API. Is it affected by v3.0?",
    "Answer": "There are no changes to Facebooks App Review policy that affect app using Facebooks Marketing API. For changes to the actual API, please see the [Graph API Changelog](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/graph-api/changelog).",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "My app is integrated with Facebooks Business Manager. Is it affected v3.0?",
    "Answer": "There are no changes to Business Manager APIs in Graph API v3.0. Apps requiring access to Business_Management permissions will require review by Facebook.",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is App Review? Do I need to submit my app?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nApps that use mediated sharing products like social plugins, share dialog and share sheets, or a subset of Facebook Login do not have to be reviewed by Facebook. To learn more about what requires review, please see our [App Review](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review) documentation.\\n\\nWe review your app to ensure a high-quality Facebook experience across apps. In general, people must be aware that they are logging in and posting to Facebook. People should be able to control the info they share with your app or back to Facebook.\\n\\nNote: People who are listed in your apps Roles tab will have access to extended permissions without going through review (e.g. manage_pages). However, when the app goes public it must go through App Review to access information even for people with roles on the app.\\n\\nAll app capabilities should be available when your app is in [Development Mode](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/register#development-mode) but you will only be able to access your data, your test users data, or your pages data. If you wish to take your app public, even if you are the only user, it must go through app review .\\n",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How can I get my review completed faster?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nDue to changes to the review process and the high volume of submissions expected, it may take several weeks for submitted apps to complete review.\\n\\nPlease provide as much info as possible to help the reviewer, including clear screenshots, detailed step-by-step instructions and a screencast recording of your app and its Facebook integration.\\n",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What instructions should I provide for the reviewer?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nYoull need to explain exactly how to test each permission or feature in your app so that we can make sure it works and follows our policies. We cant approve your app if we cant fully test how it integrates with Facebook. Giving detailed instructions makes it less likely that youll have to resubmit for review.\\n\\nFor each permission you request, list reproduction instructions in a step-by-step format. All instructions must be in English.\\n\\nYour instructions should not:\\n\\n*   \\n\\nReference instructions from other submissions or documentation\\n\\n*   \\n\\nSummarize what your app does instead of giving instructions\\n\\n*   \\n\\nProvide technical details of how your APIs work\\n\\nHeres a good example of step-by-step instructions:\\n\\n1.  Press the Settings button on the left hand menu.\\n2.  Select Login with Facebook\\n3.  Complete the third step\\n4.  Complete the fourth step\\n\\nIf youre still not sure about what to include, please see more examples in our [examples section for App Review](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review#instructions). \\n",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "I want to advertise my app with mobile app install ads. Do I need to submit for review?",
    "Answer": "No, you dont need to submit for review to run mobile app install ads. You just need an app that is live in the iTunes App Store or Google Play Store. You can follow our guide to creating [mobile app installs ads](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/ads-for-apps/mobile-app-ads).",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If my app is public, how do I test features and permissions for which my app has not been approved?",
    "Answer": "To test a new feature or permission, after your app has been [reviewed](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review) and published, use the [Create Test App feature](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/test-apps/#creating-and-managing) in the [App Dashboard](https://developers.facebook.com/apps/) to create a clone of your production app. In the Dashboard of your production app, click the down arrow next to the app name in the upper left navigation pane and click Create Test App. The app clone, created with In Development status, allows all [app roles](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/register#developer-roles) access to all features and permissions.",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do I include a test user with my submission?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\n In certain cases, you may need the reviewer to reproduce a certain behavior or experience available only to a specific test user. If this is the case, you can add this user to your submission on the App Review page. In the Items in Review section, youll see a Test User (optional) section that allows you to type the name of the user you wish to be used in your review.\\n\\nThe only test users available here are those listed as Test Users in the Roles section of your app. Please do not share Facebook login credentials for users in your review instructions.\\n\\n[Learn more](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/test-users) about how to create a test user.\\n",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "My test user cant like pages. How can I get user_likes approved in review?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\n Before approving your request for user_likes, your reviewer will need to confirm that your app provides a unique experience to users based on the like info it receives from them. To do this, our review team will test your app with a variety of test users, each with a different set of likes and interests.\\n\\nWhen submitting a request for user_likes, you should write detailed instructions that include:\\n\\n * A clear explanation of why youre requesting user_likes and how it improves a persons experience in your app. * A list of sample Pages for our reviewer to like to verify your use of user_likes. Please give direct links to the Pages that our reviewer should like before they test your app. \\n\\nIf youre using user_likes as part of an algorithm, its important that the reviewer can see the result of this algorithm and how it influences content shown to people.\\n",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How does a permission get reviewed?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\n Our review team will actually test how your app uses each permission on every platform you have listed in the settings section of your app. Your reviewer ensures that your Facebook Login integration works correctly and that each permission requested adheres to our principles and utility guidelines while providing an enhanced user experience.\\n\\nPlease see [our principles](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review#principles) and [utility guidelines](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/facebook-login/review) for more info.\\n",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What login permissions do I need for a Wordpress plugin?",
    "Answer": "Currently, apps do not require App Review if they are only used by Users who have a role on the app, and who are only publishing to their own timelines or Pages. Starting on August 1, 2018, however, apps can no longer publish to User timelines, and any apps that allow Users to publish to Groups or Pages must go through App Review.",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How can people invite their friends to use my app?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nIf your app is a game and has a presence on Facebook Canvas\\n\\nYou can invite new players to your game by using either the:\\n\\n * [Requests dialog.](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/games/services/gamerequests) When using the requests dialog you can set filters=app_non_users to filter the dialog to only show people who dont use your app. If your app has a Canvas presence, you may also use the Requests Dialog on iOS and Android. * [Invitable Friends API.](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/games/services/gamerequests) If your app is a game, and want to build your own multi-friend selector, you may use the [Invitable Friends API](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/games/invitable-friends), which returns a ranked list of the persons friends who do not use the app. Once a person has selected a number of friends to invite, you may pass the tokens returned by the Invitable Friends API to the to field of the Requests Dialog which will then let the person send an invite to those friends. \\n\\nIf your app does not have a presence on Facebook Canvas\\n\\nYou can use the [Message Dialog on iOS](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/sharing/ios) and [Android](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/sharing/android), or the [Send Dialog](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/sharing/reference/send-dialog) on Web. These products let a person [send a message](https://www.facebook.com/help/326534794098501/) directly to their friends containing a link to your app.\\n\\nThis type of message is a great channel for communicating with a smaller number of people in a direct way. The Message Dialog and the Send Dialog both include a typeahead which lets the person easily select a number of friends to receive the invite.\\n",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Do I need permissions to be re-reviewed every time I update my app?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nNo. Once youve been approved for a permission, you can use it across any version of your app on any platform.\\n\\nIf you expand and develop your app on a new platform, this will not need to be submitted for review. You only need to resubmit for review if you want to request a new permission - for example, when you add a new feature to your app. Changing and submitting your App Details or Open Graph actions will not affect the permissions youve been approved for.\\n",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What happens if I am asked to provide additional information for my request?",
    "Answer": "If your current submission requires additional information, you will have 30-days from receipt of the request to resolve and resubmit for review. During those 30-days you may be asked to provide more information by the App Review team. Please note that the 30-day window will not reset with each resubmission during this period.",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The reviewer didnt use the test user I provided. Why not?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\n Our review team uses multiple test users when reviewing submissions, and we dont always use the test user you provide. If your submission does need to be reviewed using a specific test user please let us know in your review instructions.\\n\\nIf you provide a test user, make sure youve correctly created the [test user](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/test-users) and attached the user with your submission.\\n",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "I dont agree with my review decision. What can I do?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nOur review team will use the instructions you provide to test your apps Facebook integrations.\\n\\nIf you feel our reviewer has incorrectly rejected your app, you should resubmit for review with updated review instructions that provide more info for the reviewer.\\n\\nThe review process is the best way to communicate with your reviewer by updating your notes to address the feedback youve received.\\n",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "I was rejected for a platform I didnt want to submit for review. Why?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nYour app will be reviewed on each of the platforms you list in the [Settings section](https://developers.facebook.com/apps/redirect/settings) of your App Dashboard. If you dont want a certain platform to be reviewed, including if you dont yet have a working version of your app on a specific platform, please remove it from your Settings page.\\n\\nYou can find more info in our [documentation on platforms](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review#platforms).\\n",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do I provide a screencast?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nA screencast is a great way to guide us through your app and show us how youre using the requested permissions. Heres some best practices and third party resources for [creating a screencast](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/facebook-login/review/examples#screencast).\\n\\nYour video should show how your app uses each permission it requests. If youre requesting publish_actions, it should also show how content from your app is created and shared to Facebook.\\n",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The app works for me, but not the reviewer. What can I do next?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nTo approve your app submission, our review team will need to log into your app and check all Facebook integrations.\\n\\nIf your reviewer has been unable to load or use your app, please make sure that:\\n\\n * The App URL is publicly accessible and not configured as a localhost * Youve provided the username and password needed to access your development or staging site * Your sites security certificates are up to date and not causing errors for new users * Youre able to login and use your app as a newly created test user * The items you submitted for review are built out and working in your app \\n\\nIf youre rejected again for the same reason, update your Review Instructions or Add Notes section to ask your reviewer for some clarity and additional info.\\n",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The credentials I provided are working, but the reviewer cant log in. What should I do?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nOur review team may need additional login credentials for your app in order to complete your review.\\n\\nIf your app requires a secondary login before or after Facebook Login, please be sure to provide a username and password for this. This may include login credentials for a testing or demo server, secondary login for your app or an e-mail registration flow.\\n\\nApps hosted on staging or development servers may require an additional login to access your server. Please provide all necessary login credentials for this also.\\n\\nIf youre still not sure what credentials are missing, you can provide a video with your next submission that shows the Facebook Login option and all relevant Facebook integrations youre submitting for.\\n",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "I need user_likes to know if people have liked my page. Why cant I get this approved?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nIts against [Platform Policy 4.5](https://developers.facebook.com/policy/) to incentivize people to use social plugins or to like a Page. This includes offering rewards or gating apps or app content based on whether or not a person has liked a Page. User_likes will not be approved for this purpose.\\n\\nTo ensure quality connections and help businesses reach the people who matter to them, we want people to like Pages because they want to connect and hear from the business, not because of artificial incentives. We believe this policy will benefit people and advertisers alike.\\n",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "My app was rejected because the reviewer couldnt find login, but I use the Share Dialog. Why?",
    "Answer": "If youre using the [Share Dialog](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins) or any other social plugin to publish content back to Facebook, you dont need to submit for review. If youre still not sure, you can find more info in our [general review documentation](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review).",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "My submission for App Details was rejected. How do I get approved for App Center?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nTo be approved for App Center, your App will need to meet our eligibility requirements. Apps eligible for the Facebook App Center must use Facebook Login or have a Facebook Canvas app.\\n\\nApp eligible to be listed in App Center are:\\n\\n * Apps on Facebook [Canvas](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/games/gamesonfacebook) * Mobile apps built for iOS or Android using [Facebook Login for iOS](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/facebook-login/ios) or [Facebook Login for Android](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/facebook-login/android) * Web or mobile apps using [Facebook Login](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/javascript/quickstart/v2.5) \\n\\nYour text assets and promotional images must also meet our [guidelines](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/games/appcenter).\\n",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What happens if Im not approved for a permission?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nYour review response will include a clear explanation for why your app wasnt approved, as well as the next steps you should take. We want to get you through the process as quickly as possible, so be sure to read this feedback carefully. Once you make the necessary changes, you can submit for review again.\\n\\nIf your app uses a permission in a way that isnt approvable, your feedback will explain this and you shouldnt resubmit for review.\\n",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "My app was rejected for General Issues. What does this mean?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nThe App Review process involves loading your app on each supported platform, logging in with Facebook, and using every Facebook integration that youre requesting in review. This often results in what we call general issues. These are errors or bugs relating to loading your app, logging into your app or the general functionality of your app. This means we werent able to test the permissions you request in your submission.\\n\\nSince these are issues that prevent us from reviewing your Facebook functionality, we cant comment in detail about how your app uses the Facebook functionality youve submitted for review. Because of this, we reject with General Issues and provide feedback about this on each platform.\\n\\nIf you receive a General Issues rejection, please carefully read all of the feedback. Each platform will receive individual feedback that should explain what issues were experienced in review.\\n",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What does it mean when the review team could not reproduce the permission?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nDuring the review process, our review team follows your instructions to reproduce how permissions are used within your app. If we cant reproduce this experience - for example, because we cant follow your instructions, or we cant log into your app - then we also cant approve the submission.\\n\\nTo avoid this, please:\\n\\n * Provide a working version of the app that uses the permission * Make sure your instructions in the Add Notes section are clear * Make sure that the requested login permissions personalize the user experience and comply with our principles \\n\\nIn particular, for the publish_actions permission, please confirm that your apps publishing functionality is configured correctly. We need to be able to publish your apps content back to Facebook during the review process.\\n",
    "Source": "https://developers.facebook.com/docs/apps/review/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Hi",
    "Answer": "Hello",
    "Source": "Editorial\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "qtoadd?",
    "Answer": "atoadd",
    "Source": "Editorial\r",
    "Category": "Category-10"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why is my train overcrowded?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nWe run as many peak-time trains as we can on the railway infrastructure. We adjust our timetables and the number of carriages where we can to reduce overcrowding, and were continuing to develop and improve both our train fleet and our network to improve things further. \\n\\n Trains can be busier than usual for a number of reasons. An earlier cancellation, for instance, will mean the next service will have more passengers than usual. Sometimes, trains have fewer coaches than usual because weve had to temporarily withdraw some carriages for emergency repairs. \\n\\nSee which peak-time trains are most likely to have seats available on our routes in our guide to [finding a quieter train](https://www.southernrailway.com/travel-information/travel-help/finding-a-quieter-train). \\n",
    "Source": "https://www.southernrailway.com/help-and-support/contact-us/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-4"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is Twitter?",
    "Answer": "Twitter is a service for friends, family, and coworkers to communicate and stay connected through the exchange of quick, frequent messages. People post Tweets, which may contain photos, videos, links, and text. These messages are posted to your profile, sent to your [followers](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/following-faqs), and are searchable on Twitter search. Learn more about [how to use Twitter](https://help.twitter.com/en/twitter-guide).",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-4"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Do I need anything special to use it?",
    "Answer": "All you need to use Twitter is an internet connection or a mobile phone. Join us here! Once youre in, begin finding and following accounts whose Tweets interest you. Well recommend great accounts once youre signed up.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-5"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Whats a Tweet?",
    "Answer": "A Tweet is any message posted to Twitter which may contain photos, videos, links, and text. Click or tap the Tweet button to post the update to your profile. Read our [Posting a Tweet](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/how-to-tweet) article for more information.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-5"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How can I send updates to Twitter?",
    "Answer": "Read our article about [how to post a Tweet](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/how-to-tweet). You can Tweet from twitter.com, a mobile device, or an application.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-5"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Whats a Retweet?",
    "Answer": "A [Retweet](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/retweet-faqs) is a Tweet that you forward to your followers.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-5"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do I post a picture to Twitter?",
    "Answer": "Uploading and sharing images on Twitter is easy! Find step-by-step instructions and FAQs on [how to post a picture on Twitter](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/tweeting-gifs-and-pictures).",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-5"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Can I edit a Tweet once Ive posted it?",
    "Answer": "No, you cant edit a Tweet once you have posted it, but you can [delete your Tweet](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/delete-tweets).",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-5"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How can I enable night mode?",
    "Answer": "To enable night mode via twitter.com, click on your profile photo, then select Night mode from the drop-down menu. To disable night mode, simply click on the Night mode setting again. Night mode is also available on [Twitter for iOS](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/twitter-ios-app#night-mode) and [Twitter for Android.](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/twitter-for-android-faqs#night)",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-5"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who reads my updates?",
    "Answer": "Your followers read your Tweets. If your Tweets are public, anyone who runs a search for a keyword in your Tweet may be able to see that message. Your Tweets are public by default; if youre hesitant to have people you may not know read your updates, [protect your Tweets](https://help.twitter.com/en/safety-and-security/public-and-protected-tweets) to approve followers and keep your updates out of search.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-5"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why cant I see all my Tweets? Are they lost?",
    "Answer": "We store all your Tweets. Navigate to your profile to view up to 3,200 of your most recent Tweets in your profile timeline. To view more, you can [download your Twitter Archive](https://help.twitter.com/en/managing-your-account/how-to-download-your-twitter-archive) and browse a snapshot of your Twitter information, starting with your first Tweet.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-5"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Can I put my Twitter updates on my blog?",
    "Answer": "Yes! Put a [Twitter widget](https://twitter.com/settings/widgets) on your blog or website - anywhere that accepts Javascript or HTML.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-5"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What does it mean to follow someone on Twitter?",
    "Answer": "[Following](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/following-faqs) someone means youve chosen to subscribe to their Twitter updates. When you follow someone, every time they post a new message, it will appear on your Twitter Home timeline.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-5"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do I find people to follow?",
    "Answer": "When you create an account, you can [search for people](https://twitter.com/#!/who_to_follow/suggestions) by name or username, [import friends](https://twitter.com/#!/who_to_follow/import) from other networks, or [invite friends via email](https://twitter.com/#!/who_to_follow/import).",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-6"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do I know who Im following?",
    "Answer": "After you click or tap the Follow button on someones profile, youre following them. See a list of people youre following by clicking on the [following](https://twitter.com/#!/following) link on your profile page or on your home pages sidebar.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-6"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do I know who is following me?",
    "Answer": "Twitter sends you a notification when someone new follows you. Set up your [email preferences](https://help.twitter.com/en/managing-your-account/updating-email-preferences) and [mobile push notifications](https://help.twitter.com/en/managing-your-account/notifications-on-mobile-devices) to notify you when you have a new follower. The [Followers](https://twitter.com/followers) link on your profile page will also tell you who is following you.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-6"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What are follow limits?",
    "Answer": "Twitter has follow and update limits for stability and abuse control. Learn more about [follow limits](https://help.twitter.com/en/rules-and-policies/twitter-limits).",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-6"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What are replies?",
    "Answer": "A [reply](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/mentions-and-replies) is a response to another persons Tweet. Click or tap the reply icon on another persons Tweet to reply to it. Please note that if your Tweets are protected, people who are not following you will not see your replies or mentions.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-7"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the difference between a reply and a Direct Message?",
    "Answer": "A [reply](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/mentions-and-replies) is a public message sent regardless of follow-ship. Anyone can view it (if your Tweets are public). A [Direct Message](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/direct-messages) is a private message, and can only be seen by the sender and intended recipients.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-7"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What are Direct Messages?",
    "Answer": "[Direct Messages](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/direct-messages) are private messages sent from one Twitter account to other Twitter account(s), and they do not appear in public for anyone else to read. You can start a conversation with anyone who follows you.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-7"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why are accounts suspended?",
    "Answer": "Accounts are suspended for [Terms of Service](https://twitter.com/tos?lang=en) violations or spam investigation. Read more [about account suspension](https://help.twitter.com/en/managing-your-account/suspended-twitter-accounts).",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-7"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do I report spam?",
    "Answer": "Read our article about [how to report spam on Twitter](https://help.twitter.com/en/safety-and-security/report-spam). We encourage you to always block any spammers you find.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-7"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Where can I find out more information about Twitters Terms of Service?",
    "Answer": "Read Twitters [Terms of Service](https://twitter.com/tos?lang=en) and the [Twitter Rules](https://help.twitter.com/en/rules-and-policies/twitter-rules) for more information.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do I submit a complaint about copyright, impersonation, trademark, or other Terms of Service issues?",
    "Answer": "Review our [Terms of Service section](https://help.twitter.com/en/rules-and-policies/twitter-trademark-policy) to find out what constitutes a violation, and how to go about fixing a related problem.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Hi",
    "Answer": "Hello",
    "Source": "Editorial\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is GitHub Enterprise?",
    "Answer": "GitHub Enterprise is the on-premises version of [GitHub.com](https://github.com/home). It makes collaborative coding possible and enjoyable for large-scale enterprise software development teams. A full list of specs and features are detailed on our [data sheet](https://enterprise.github.com/downloads/en/enterprise-datasheet.pdf).",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How is GitHub Enterprise different from",
    "Answer": "[GitHub.com](http://github.com/)?",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Can I evaluate GitHub Enterprise within my organization before purchasing?",
    "Answer": "Yes. 45-day evaluation licenses are available and may be upgraded to full licenses at any time during the trial period. To get started, [try GitHub for free](https://enterprise.github.com/trial). Well contact you shortly after with information on downloading the software and installing trial license keys.",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What hardware and software are required?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nGitHub Enterprise is delivered as a virtual appliance that includes all software required to get up and running. The only additional software required is a compatible virtual machine environment.\\n\\nThe following minimal hardware requirements are suggested for production deployments:\\n\\n*   Processor: Two 3.0 GHz CPU cores (or virtual equivalent) \\n*   Memory: 14-16 GB (minimum dependent on selected platform) \\n*   Disk: \\n\\n    *   200 GB VM root partition \\n    *   100 GB data partition (our recommendation, actual size depends on your data) \\n*   Storage: High-performance SAN or locally attached storage",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is a Virtual Appliance?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nYou can think of a virtual appliance as the equivalent of a network appliance that you might buy, mount in a rack, and plug into your network. The only difference is that it runs as a virtual machine inside of VMware or some other virtualization platform rather than as a physical device you mount in a rack.\\n\\nThis saves time (you can download the appliance and all updates immediately) and space (you just add it to your existing virtualization infrastructure). It also makes managing, backing up, and restoring the appliance easy because you can use your virtualization platforms built-in snapshotting capabilities. \\n\\nYou can learn more about virtual appliances [here](http://www.vmware.com/appliances/getting-started/learn/overview.html).\\n",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which Virtual Machine environments are supported?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nWe currently support the following environments.\\nPlatformImage Format[VMware](https://www.vmware.com/)[OVF](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Open_Virtualization_Format)[OpenStack KVM](https://www.openstack.org/)[QCOW2](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Qcow#qcow2)[XenServer](http://www.xenserver.org/)[VHD](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/VHD_(file_format)#Software_support)[Hyper-V](https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/server-cloud/solutions/virtualization.aspx)[VHD](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/VHD_(file_format)#Software_support)[Microsoft Azure](https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/)[VHD](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/VHD_(file_format)#Software_support)[Amazon Web Services (AWS)](https://aws.amazon.com/)[AMI](https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/AMIs.html)[Google Cloud Platform (GCP)](https://cloud.google.com/)[Google Compute Engine (GCE) image](https://cloud.google.com/compute/docs/images)\\n\\nPlease [contact us](https://enterprise.github.com/contact) if we dont support your environment.\\n",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Does GitHub Enterprise support clustering?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nYes, as of [GitHub Enterprise 2.5](https://enterprise.github.com/releases/2.5.0). However, clustering is designed for specific scaling situations and is not intended for every organization.\\n\\nPlease refer to the [Clustering Guide](https://help.github.com/enterprise/admin/guides/clustering) to learn more about clustering.\\n",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Is clustering right for my organization?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nClustering provides better scalability by distributing load across multiple nodes. This horizontal scaling may be preferable for some organizations with tens of thousands of developers. However, setting up a redundant and scalable cluster can be complex and requires careful planning. This additional complexity will need to be planned for during installation, disaster recovery scenarios, and upgrades.\\n\\nGitHub Enterprise requires low latency between nodes and is not intended for redundancy across geographic locations.\\n\\nClustering provides redundancy, but it is not intended to replace the [High Availability Configuration](https://help.github.com/enterprise/admin/guides/installation/high-availability-configuration). A primary/secondary failover configuration is far simpler than clustering and will serve the needs of many organizations.\\n",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do I get access to clustering?",
    "Answer": "Clustering is designed for specific scaling situations and is not intended for every organization. If clustering is something youd like to consider, please contact your dedicated representative or our [account management team](mailto:sales@github.com) at [sales@github.com](mailto:sales@github.com).",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Can we authenticate users with our LDAP directory or identity access management system?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\n Yes. GitHub Enterprise supports external user authentication via LDAP, CAS, or SAML. The setup process includes a step for configuring your organizations identity management information. \\n\\nBy default, GitHub Enterprise runs in a self-contained authentication mode with user information stored in the GitHub Enterprise database. LDAP, SAML, or CAS is not required.\\n",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which LDAP providers are supported?",
    "Answer": "GitHub Enterprise supports any provider that follows the LDAP specification. See [this article](https://help.github.com/enterprise/admin/guides/user-management/using-ldap/#supported-ldap-services) for a full list of supported providers.",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which SAML providers are supported?",
    "Answer": "GitHub Enterprise supports any provider that follows the SAML 2.0 standard. See [this article](https://help.github.com/enterprise/admin/guides/user-management/using-saml/) for a full list of supported providers.",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do I control access to Git repositories?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nThe product includes a number of features that provide granular control over repository access. Each repository may specify the following general access rights for each team or collaborator:\\n\\n*   Admin: Full access to the repository, including the ability to control access for other users.\\n*   Read + Write: Users may push changes into the repository and pull changes from the repository.\\n*   Read-only: Users may browse the repository via the web interface and use Git to fetch changes but may not push into the repository.\\n\\nIn addition to these access levels, you can use protected branches inside a repository to prevent force pushes to specific branches. You can also define individuals or teams who are allowed to push to a branch, preventing others from making changes.\\n\\nRequired statuses offer more control over changes made in protected branches. Using required statuses, you can disable the ability to merge changes into protected branches until certain CI checks pass.\\n\\nGitHub Enterprise ships with the same [collaboration features for Organizations](https://github.com/features) found on GitHub.com. These simplify the process of managing access for teams of users that you define.\\n",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why is my train overcrowded?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nWe run as many peak-time trains as we can on the railway infrastructure. We adjust our timetables and the number of carriages where we can to reduce overcrowding, and were continuing to develop and improve both our train fleet and our network to improve things further. \\n\\n Trains can be busier than usual for a number of reasons. An earlier cancellation, for instance, will mean the next service will have more passengers than usual. Sometimes, trains have fewer coaches than usual because weve had to temporarily withdraw some carriages for emergency repairs. \\n\\nSee which peak-time trains are most likely to have seats available on our routes in our guide to [finding a quieter train](https://www.southernrailway.com/travel-information/travel-help/finding-a-quieter-train). \\n",
    "Source": "https://www.southernrailway.com/help-and-support/contact-us/faqs\r",
    "Category": "Category-4"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is Twitter?",
    "Answer": "Twitter is a service for friends, family, and coworkers to communicate and stay connected through the exchange of quick, frequent messages. People post Tweets, which may contain photos, videos, links, and text. These messages are posted to your profile, sent to your [followers](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/following-faqs), and are searchable on Twitter search. Learn more about [how to use Twitter](https://help.twitter.com/en/twitter-guide).",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-4"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Do I need anything special to use it?",
    "Answer": "All you need to use Twitter is an internet connection or a mobile phone. Join us here! Once youre in, begin finding and following accounts whose Tweets interest you. Well recommend great accounts once youre signed up.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-5"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Whats a Tweet?",
    "Answer": "A Tweet is any message posted to Twitter which may contain photos, videos, links, and text. Click or tap the Tweet button to post the update to your profile. Read our [Posting a Tweet](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/how-to-tweet) article for more information.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-5"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How can I send updates to Twitter?",
    "Answer": "Read our article about [how to post a Tweet](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/how-to-tweet). You can Tweet from twitter.com, a mobile device, or an application.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-5"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Whats a Retweet?",
    "Answer": "A [Retweet](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/retweet-faqs) is a Tweet that you forward to your followers.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-5"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do I post a picture to Twitter?",
    "Answer": "Uploading and sharing images on Twitter is easy! Find step-by-step instructions and FAQs on [how to post a picture on Twitter](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/tweeting-gifs-and-pictures).",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-5"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Can I edit a Tweet once Ive posted it?",
    "Answer": "No, you cant edit a Tweet once you have posted it, but you can [delete your Tweet](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/delete-tweets).",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-5"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How can I enable night mode?",
    "Answer": "To enable night mode via twitter.com, click on your profile photo, then select Night mode from the drop-down menu. To disable night mode, simply click on the Night mode setting again. Night mode is also available on [Twitter for iOS](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/twitter-ios-app#night-mode) and [Twitter for Android.](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/twitter-for-android-faqs#night)",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-5"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who reads my updates?",
    "Answer": "Your followers read your Tweets. If your Tweets are public, anyone who runs a search for a keyword in your Tweet may be able to see that message. Your Tweets are public by default; if youre hesitant to have people you may not know read your updates, [protect your Tweets](https://help.twitter.com/en/safety-and-security/public-and-protected-tweets) to approve followers and keep your updates out of search.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-5"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why cant I see all my Tweets? Are they lost?",
    "Answer": "We store all your Tweets. Navigate to your profile to view up to 3,200 of your most recent Tweets in your profile timeline. To view more, you can [download your Twitter Archive](https://help.twitter.com/en/managing-your-account/how-to-download-your-twitter-archive) and browse a snapshot of your Twitter information, starting with your first Tweet.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-5"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Can I put my Twitter updates on my blog?",
    "Answer": "Yes! Put a [Twitter widget](https://twitter.com/settings/widgets) on your blog or website - anywhere that accepts Javascript or HTML.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-5"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What does it mean to follow someone on Twitter?",
    "Answer": "[Following](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/following-faqs) someone means youve chosen to subscribe to their Twitter updates. When you follow someone, every time they post a new message, it will appear on your Twitter Home timeline.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-5"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do I find people to follow?",
    "Answer": "When you create an account, you can [search for people](https://twitter.com/#!/who_to_follow/suggestions) by name or username, [import friends](https://twitter.com/#!/who_to_follow/import) from other networks, or [invite friends via email](https://twitter.com/#!/who_to_follow/import).",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-6"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do I know who Im following?",
    "Answer": "After you click or tap the Follow button on someones profile, youre following them. See a list of people youre following by clicking on the [following](https://twitter.com/#!/following) link on your profile page or on your home pages sidebar.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-6"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do I know who is following me?",
    "Answer": "Twitter sends you a notification when someone new follows you. Set up your [email preferences](https://help.twitter.com/en/managing-your-account/updating-email-preferences) and [mobile push notifications](https://help.twitter.com/en/managing-your-account/notifications-on-mobile-devices) to notify you when you have a new follower. The [Followers](https://twitter.com/followers) link on your profile page will also tell you who is following you.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-6"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What are follow limits?",
    "Answer": "Twitter has follow and update limits for stability and abuse control. Learn more about [follow limits](https://help.twitter.com/en/rules-and-policies/twitter-limits).",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-6"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What are replies?",
    "Answer": "A [reply](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/mentions-and-replies) is a response to another persons Tweet. Click or tap the reply icon on another persons Tweet to reply to it. Please note that if your Tweets are protected, people who are not following you will not see your replies or mentions.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-7"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the difference between a reply and a Direct Message?",
    "Answer": "A [reply](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/mentions-and-replies) is a public message sent regardless of follow-ship. Anyone can view it (if your Tweets are public). A [Direct Message](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/direct-messages) is a private message, and can only be seen by the sender and intended recipients.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-7"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What are Direct Messages?",
    "Answer": "[Direct Messages](https://help.twitter.com/en/using-twitter/direct-messages) are private messages sent from one Twitter account to other Twitter account(s), and they do not appear in public for anyone else to read. You can start a conversation with anyone who follows you.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-7"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why are accounts suspended?",
    "Answer": "Accounts are suspended for [Terms of Service](https://twitter.com/tos?lang=en) violations or spam investigation. Read more [about account suspension](https://help.twitter.com/en/managing-your-account/suspended-twitter-accounts).",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-7"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do I report spam?",
    "Answer": "Read our article about [how to report spam on Twitter](https://help.twitter.com/en/safety-and-security/report-spam). We encourage you to always block any spammers you find.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-7"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Where can I find out more information about Twitters Terms of Service?",
    "Answer": "Read Twitters [Terms of Service](https://twitter.com/tos?lang=en) and the [Twitter Rules](https://help.twitter.com/en/rules-and-policies/twitter-rules) for more information.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do I submit a complaint about copyright, impersonation, trademark, or other Terms of Service issues?",
    "Answer": "Review our [Terms of Service section](https://help.twitter.com/en/rules-and-policies/twitter-trademark-policy) to find out what constitutes a violation, and how to go about fixing a related problem.",
    "Source": "https://help.twitter.com/en/new-user-faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Hi",
    "Answer": "Hello",
    "Source": "Editorial\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is GitHub Enterprise?",
    "Answer": "GitHub Enterprise is the on-premises version of [GitHub.com](https://github.com/home). It makes collaborative coding possible and enjoyable for large-scale enterprise software development teams. A full list of specs and features are detailed on our [data sheet](https://enterprise.github.com/downloads/en/enterprise-datasheet.pdf).",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How is GitHub Enterprise different from",
    "Answer": "[GitHub.com](http://github.com/)?",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Can I evaluate GitHub Enterprise within my organization before purchasing?",
    "Answer": "Yes. 45-day evaluation licenses are available and may be upgraded to full licenses at any time during the trial period. To get started, [try GitHub for free](https://enterprise.github.com/trial). Well contact you shortly after with information on downloading the software and installing trial license keys.",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What hardware and software are required?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nGitHub Enterprise is delivered as a virtual appliance that includes all software required to get up and running. The only additional software required is a compatible virtual machine environment.\\n\\nThe following minimal hardware requirements are suggested for production deployments:\\n\\n*   Processor: Two 3.0 GHz CPU cores (or virtual equivalent) \\n*   Memory: 14-16 GB (minimum dependent on selected platform) \\n*   Disk: \\n\\n    *   200 GB VM root partition \\n    *   100 GB data partition (our recommendation, actual size depends on your data) \\n*   Storage: High-performance SAN or locally attached storage",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is a Virtual Appliance?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nYou can think of a virtual appliance as the equivalent of a network appliance that you might buy, mount in a rack, and plug into your network. The only difference is that it runs as a virtual machine inside of VMware or some other virtualization platform rather than as a physical device you mount in a rack.\\n\\nThis saves time (you can download the appliance and all updates immediately) and space (you just add it to your existing virtualization infrastructure). It also makes managing, backing up, and restoring the appliance easy because you can use your virtualization platforms built-in snapshotting capabilities. \\n\\nYou can learn more about virtual appliances [here](http://www.vmware.com/appliances/getting-started/learn/overview.html).\\n",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which Virtual Machine environments are supported?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nWe currently support the following environments.\\nPlatformImage Format[VMware](https://www.vmware.com/)[OVF](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Open_Virtualization_Format)[OpenStack KVM](https://www.openstack.org/)[QCOW2](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Qcow#qcow2)[XenServer](http://www.xenserver.org/)[VHD](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/VHD_(file_format)#Software_support)[Hyper-V](https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/server-cloud/solutions/virtualization.aspx)[VHD](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/VHD_(file_format)#Software_support)[Microsoft Azure](https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/)[VHD](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/VHD_(file_format)#Software_support)[Amazon Web Services (AWS)](https://aws.amazon.com/)[AMI](https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/AMIs.html)[Google Cloud Platform (GCP)](https://cloud.google.com/)[Google Compute Engine (GCE) image](https://cloud.google.com/compute/docs/images)\\n\\nPlease [contact us](https://enterprise.github.com/contact) if we dont support your environment.\\n",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Does GitHub Enterprise support clustering?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nYes, as of [GitHub Enterprise 2.5](https://enterprise.github.com/releases/2.5.0). However, clustering is designed for specific scaling situations and is not intended for every organization.\\n\\nPlease refer to the [Clustering Guide](https://help.github.com/enterprise/admin/guides/clustering) to learn more about clustering.\\n",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Is clustering right for my organization?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nClustering provides better scalability by distributing load across multiple nodes. This horizontal scaling may be preferable for some organizations with tens of thousands of developers. However, setting up a redundant and scalable cluster can be complex and requires careful planning. This additional complexity will need to be planned for during installation, disaster recovery scenarios, and upgrades.\\n\\nGitHub Enterprise requires low latency between nodes and is not intended for redundancy across geographic locations.\\n\\nClustering provides redundancy, but it is not intended to replace the [High Availability Configuration](https://help.github.com/enterprise/admin/guides/installation/high-availability-configuration). A primary/secondary failover configuration is far simpler than clustering and will serve the needs of many organizations.\\n",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do I get access to clustering?",
    "Answer": "Clustering is designed for specific scaling situations and is not intended for every organization. If clustering is something youd like to consider, please contact your dedicated representative or our [account management team](mailto:sales@github.com) at [sales@github.com](mailto:sales@github.com).",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Can we authenticate users with our LDAP directory or identity access management system?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\n Yes. GitHub Enterprise supports external user authentication via LDAP, CAS, or SAML. The setup process includes a step for configuring your organizations identity management information. \\n\\nBy default, GitHub Enterprise runs in a self-contained authentication mode with user information stored in the GitHub Enterprise database. LDAP, SAML, or CAS is not required.\\n",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which LDAP providers are supported?",
    "Answer": "GitHub Enterprise supports any provider that follows the LDAP specification. See [this article](https://help.github.com/enterprise/admin/guides/user-management/using-ldap/#supported-ldap-services) for a full list of supported providers.",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which SAML providers are supported?",
    "Answer": "GitHub Enterprise supports any provider that follows the SAML 2.0 standard. See [this article](https://help.github.com/enterprise/admin/guides/user-management/using-saml/) for a full list of supported providers.",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do I control access to Git repositories?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nThe product includes a number of features that provide granular control over repository access. Each repository may specify the following general access rights for each team or collaborator:\\n\\n*   Admin: Full access to the repository, including the ability to control access for other users.\\n*   Read + Write: Users may push changes into the repository and pull changes from the repository.\\n*   Read-only: Users may browse the repository via the web interface and use Git to fetch changes but may not push into the repository.\\n\\nIn addition to these access levels, you can use protected branches inside a repository to prevent force pushes to specific branches. You can also define individuals or teams who are allowed to push to a branch, preventing others from making changes.\\n\\nRequired statuses offer more control over changes made in protected branches. Using required statuses, you can disable the ability to merge changes into protected branches until certain CI checks pass.\\n\\nGitHub Enterprise ships with the same [collaboration features for Organizations](https://github.com/features) found on GitHub.com. These simplify the process of managing access for teams of users that you define.\\n",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which Virtual Machine environments are supported?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nWe currently support the following environments.\\nPlatformImage Format[VMware](https://www.vmware.com/)[OVF](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Open_Virtualization_Format)[OpenStack KVM](https://www.openstack.org/)[QCOW2](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Qcow#qcow2)[XenServer](http://www.xenserver.org/)[VHD](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/VHD_(file_format)#Software_support)[Hyper-V](https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/server-cloud/solutions/virtualization.aspx)[VHD](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/VHD_(file_format)#Software_support)[Microsoft Azure](https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/)[VHD](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/VHD_(file_format)#Software_support)[Amazon Web Services (AWS)](https://aws.amazon.com/)[AMI](https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/AMIs.html)[Google Cloud Platform (GCP)](https://cloud.google.com/)[Google Compute Engine (GCE) image](https://cloud.google.com/compute/docs/images)\\n\\nPlease [contact us](https://enterprise.github.com/contact) if we dont support your environment.\\n",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Does GitHub Enterprise support clustering?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nYes, as of [GitHub Enterprise 2.5](https://enterprise.github.com/releases/2.5.0). However, clustering is designed for specific scaling situations and is not intended for every organization.\\n\\nPlease refer to the [Clustering Guide](https://help.github.com/enterprise/admin/guides/clustering) to learn more about clustering.\\n",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Is clustering right for my organization?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nClustering provides better scalability by distributing load across multiple nodes. This horizontal scaling may be preferable for some organizations with tens of thousands of developers. However, setting up a redundant and scalable cluster can be complex and requires careful planning. This additional complexity will need to be planned for during installation, disaster recovery scenarios, and upgrades.\\n\\nGitHub Enterprise requires low latency between nodes and is not intended for redundancy across geographic locations.\\n\\nClustering provides redundancy, but it is not intended to replace the [High Availability Configuration](https://help.github.com/enterprise/admin/guides/installation/high-availability-configuration). A primary/secondary failover configuration is far simpler than clustering and will serve the needs of many organizations.\\n",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do I get access to clustering?",
    "Answer": "Clustering is designed for specific scaling situations and is not intended for every organization. If clustering is something youd like to consider, please contact your dedicated representative or our [account management team](mailto:sales@github.com) at [sales@github.com](mailto:sales@github.com).",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Can we authenticate users with our LDAP directory or identity access management system?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\n Yes. GitHub Enterprise supports external user authentication via LDAP, CAS, or SAML. The setup process includes a step for configuring your organizations identity management information. \\n\\nBy default, GitHub Enterprise runs in a self-contained authentication mode with user information stored in the GitHub Enterprise database. LDAP, SAML, or CAS is not required.\\n",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-8"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which LDAP providers are supported?",
    "Answer": "GitHub Enterprise supports any provider that follows the LDAP specification. See [this article](https://help.github.com/enterprise/admin/guides/user-management/using-ldap/#supported-ldap-services) for a full list of supported providers.",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which SAML providers are supported?",
    "Answer": "GitHub Enterprise supports any provider that follows the SAML 2.0 standard. See [this article](https://help.github.com/enterprise/admin/guides/user-management/using-saml/) for a full list of supported providers.",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do I control access to Git repositories?",
    "Answer": "\\n\\nThe product includes a number of features that provide granular control over repository access. Each repository may specify the following general access rights for each team or collaborator:\\n\\n*   Admin: Full access to the repository, including the ability to control access for other users.\\n*   Read + Write: Users may push changes into the repository and pull changes from the repository.\\n*   Read-only: Users may browse the repository via the web interface and use Git to fetch changes but may not push into the repository.\\n\\nIn addition to these access levels, you can use protected branches inside a repository to prevent force pushes to specific branches. You can also define individuals or teams who are allowed to push to a branch, preventing others from making changes.\\n\\nRequired statuses offer more control over changes made in protected branches. Using required statuses, you can disable the ability to merge changes into protected branches until certain CI checks pass.\\n\\nGitHub Enterprise ships with the same [collaboration features for Organizations](https://github.com/features) found on GitHub.com. These simplify the process of managing access for teams of users that you define.\\n",
    "Source": "https://enterprise.github.com/faq\r",
    "Category": "Category-9"
  }
]
